<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Yahtzee</string>
    <string name="yahtzee_intro">Welcome to Yahtzee! Follow instructions to play the game. Help will be available when appropriate via a button at the bottom of the screen. Press next to continue.</string>
    <string name="determine_player">Roll to determine who will go first. Player die is on the left, and computer on the right.</string>
    <string name="round">"Round: "</string>
    <string name="determine_player_tie">You and the computer tied! Please roll again.</string>
    <string name="determine_player_human">You will go first.</string>
    <string name="determine_player_comp">The computer will go first.</string>
    <string name="roll_button_desc">Roll randomly on left; manual input on right.</string>
    <string name="roll_instruction">Click the left button to roll dice; click the right button to manually input roll.</string>
    <string name="reroll_instruction_human">Locked dice are displayed in red. Select unlocked dice to reroll; they will be highlighted in blue. If none are selected, you must stand.</string>
    <string name="stand_instruction_comp">The computer has decided to stand. Press next to continue.</string>
    <string name="available_categories_instructions_human">Please select all available categories given the dice set below.</string>
    <string name="available_categories_instructions_computer">The computer has selected all available categories given the dice set below.</string>
    <string name="error">An error ocurred.</string>
    <string name="incorrect_available">Incorrect categories selected. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="roll">"Roll: "</string>
    <string name="hum_score">"Your score: "</string>
    <string name="comp_score">"Computer\'s score: "</string>
    <string name="pursue_categories_instructions_human">Please select which category or categories to pursue.</string>
    <string name="select_category_instructions_human">Please select a category to fill.</string>
    <string name="no_categories">There are no available categories to fill. Please proceed to the next turn.</string>
    <string name="no_category_error">Error: Please select a category to fill.</string>
    <string name="wrong_scorecard_inputs_error">Incorrect input for Round or Points Earned. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="round_summary">The round has ended. See the summary below.</string>
</resources>